half ass I don't know anyone that wants
to do that um I was I'm going to kind of
flip the change the the the conversation
here and I want to get to know you I
want to I want to know what like all cuz
I mean Dave Daly the monster motivator
is
247 so on the few hours that you do get
to yourself what do you do uh well I'm
up at my alarm goes off at 4:30 every
morning seven days a week I'm at the gym
um and that's my hour of that's my zen
that's and that's 7 days a week uh
unless I'm traveling and then if I have
to do it later in the day but that's my
zen that's that's that's that's my
centering and then from there my day
unfolds and one of the things I love um
I'm a big MMA guy I love um MMA and I
love the UFC so my downtime would be
like that Saturday night pay-per-view uh
MMA um uh fight either going there or or
watching it uh with with friends uh but
but honestly I'm a worker man I'm my
assistant called me it was a Sunday two
weeks ago like 3:00 in the afternoon and
she said I just want to make sure I'm
not bothering I said Cindy I have no
boundaries look to me Sunday is just
like a Tuesday and that's and
understanding see getting back to what
you said Ryan about your own level of
awareness that might not work for
everybody right Sunday might be your day
for your family you got to figure that
out right and and mold around around
that for me if I got stuff to do I'm
getting [ __ ] done on Sunday right it's
quiet I'm going to knock it out and then
move forward and I also have another
business that I've run I have a fire
restoration business out here so you
know a lot of balls in the air but
that's what that's my oxygen that's what
keeps me interested and I realized when
I got out of high school when I could
look back and clear my head and start to
see success I realized that they just
didn't they didn't keep my attention I
was bored out of my mind you don't know
why I was bored because I didn't see any
purpose I didn't see any end result when
you're running when you're starting a
business there's a purpose there's a
direction there's a road map and then
there's a destination right for school
it's like you're just going through the
motions understand the basics right the
reading uh math the basic skills that
has to be implemented but everything El
after that really should be somehow
customized to that person man because
because I was bored out of my mind and
that's most entrepreneurs they and we
hate to be told what to do that's right
it's in our DNA and I was going to just
mention that because a lot of people
think that we're
self-absorbed um especially if we're in
the public eye and we're speaking and
and whatnot and yes I am
self-absorbed because you know I believe
that that's just my level of confidence
however there's always a however there
are people in our life that keep us
balanced okay we're live this is Ryan
Perez AKA AKA RP to God AKA The Wizard
you know why because I make [ __ ] happen
uh today okay
folks folks we got in um a guy that I
admire um you know he's been a part of
the hustle own group on Facebook uh he's
been a part of some of my other friends
uh um you know live broadcast and he's
been participating in this community
that we've developed uh with people that
are are just taking action I want to
intr juice well first we got to say
welcome to the hustle Zone and we got to
welcome Dave Daly the the monster
motivator so welcome Dave how's it going
my friend what's up big man what's up I
love the way you introduced this you
know I'll tell you why this is going to
be an epic epic show because you your um
your name is making [ __ ] happen right
yes that's right okay go on when you get
a chance guys go on to my website
monster motivator TV and it's going to
say making [ __ ] happen baby so I love it
man knuckle that up big man love it nice
nice well yeah you know so so Dave the
first question that we normally ask our
guest like I want to like just to give
everyone the premise of the show um uh
hustle zone is capturing the essence of
entrepreneurs because a lot of a lot of
people don't really understand the guts
behind uh the people that are making
moves that are making things happen
right most entrepreneurs are ask well
can you do this for me can you do that
for me but no one really tries to
understand the human side of of being an
entrepreneur and the struggles uh uh the
spirit that goes into to to making
things happen the way that they do you
know like not everyone has the the guts
to to to take on risk and these are the
people that I align myself with they
they take the risk they put themselves
out there and they change the world at
the same time so the first question that
we normally ask our guests is
what is your story so Dave there there
lace up your boots man this is going to
be this is gonna be a rough ride you
know um I tell my story a lot so it's
it's real um it's what I call it's been
a rough paper route and to truth be told
Ryan I'm not even really supposed to be
here you know my early years were
nothing close to successful left back in
the second grade diagnosed with ADD said
I had a learning disorder never
graduated high school
and at 19 I'm sitting in a jail cell
looking at 8 to 10 if things don't go my
way and that was just that was just the
beginning stages so um and I'm I'm true
I'm a complete and utter believer that
struggle equals strength as long as you
have this perspective you're either
going to win or you're going to learn
and if you look at it any other way
you're going to lose so when it comes to
cuz I I mean I was diagnosed with ADD
and you know I'm dyslexic and there's
all kinds of things that happened when I
was in school and they weren't like the
teachers were not really equipped um in
recognizing how to deal with that
because I honestly feel that it's not a
disability that it is it's it's an
ability that a lot of people don't have
because our brains they go fast and
they're thinking of we're we're
multi-dimensional in the way that we
think and that we learn and and most of
us are geniuses to be honest with you
because it I hear the same story it just
seems to be a common thing on the hustle
Zone where people just come from the
background that they were you know add
they had dyslexia but yet they're super
smart or they have crazy businesses so
how like let's dig deeper you know when
you said you had add and you were
growing up you're in high school high
school dropout like what was going
through your mind during those times and
and um like what do you
remember uh about your childhood well
you know growing up I had a pretty
normal childhood if you would if you
will but you know what really saved me
was was sports right I started wrestling
in fourth grade I was that physical kid
I wanted to be outside playing sports
doing things that were physical that was
my comfort zone but you put me in that
classroom and it was just so confining
that I just you know I just wanted to
jump out that window and run and uh and
at the same time because I couldn't
learn in that cookie cutter mode growing
up you're told that you're not supposed
to win don't expect a lot out of
yourself and that's why I'm a big
believer that personal development
self-help help needs to be taught from
day one because everything that I talk
about everything that I uh all my
message maps to one thing Ryan it maps
to your self image because you could
build it up you could tear it down but
you cannot outperform it and when you
can build a child self-image and create
that bulletproof self-image there's
nothing that they're not going to be
able to do if they apply themselves and
you in in you insert that work ethic
right when you have that com
you you're you're absolutely Unstoppable
in whatever you want to do the problem
is you're conditioning as you grow up
build yourself image and if it's not
that strong powerful selft talk that
you've been told that conditioning over
and over then what happens is as an
adult you have a decision you can either
learn how to change that or you keep
that same tape playing over and over and
over in your head because I had a
decision I could have still been that
Dropout I could have still been the guy
That was supposed to win I could have
still been just a laborer in
construction right but some some some
things happen in my life that life says
here's your boot camp are you going to
make it on the other end when you make
it on the other end if you make it to
the other end here's the decision here's
the choices you have life always gives
you choices and I say this Ryan you
don't make the rules I don't make the
rules life makes the rules and life says
you got to earn it if you want it m so
when when
um when you were young what parts of of
uh or like when you were in high school
what
parts did you when did you recognize
that you were different that you that
you could do that you knew that you
could do something different that the
school system wasn't going to serve you
like what was the period where you
realized that um that you needed to make
a change well I think I think it was um
even earlier than that for some reason
uh there was a part of me that that was
buying into hey maybe you're not smart
enough maybe you're not supposed to win
but there was also another part of me to
be honest with you that did my thing
like in other words I loved wrestling
right so the big sport when we were
little M uh uh uh was baseball right I
did two seasons that I was bored out of
my mind I hated it it was like watching
paint dry out in the field right I it
just wasn't for me but you put me in the
wrestling room put me in the in on the
mat and it just things changed but and
then some other things like um I always
I didn't have to go down the road of
everyone else for whatever reason I knew
what I liked I knew what worked for me
and I think early on that's a great
foundation and where that came from I'm
not really sure I can't pinpoint that
but it's such a great foundation for an
entrepreneur because listen when you're
going after something that scares you
and excites you at the same time you're
going to their circle is going to want
to put you in a straight jacket they're
going to think you're out of your mind
I'll give you a great example I I
relocated out here to San Diego from New
Jersey um in 2008 when I came out in
2008 I wasn't sure what business I was
going to do but I made a deal with
myself and I said if I'm G to make this
big move it's going to be it's going to
be passion related then profit related
second my other business were always
about the profit right so I actually
bought a struggling Sports nutrition
store in North County Vista now I never
had a retail business knew nobody out
here moved across the country and they
were struggling in 2008 2009 it was a
depression not a recession so everyone
that knew me thought I lost my mind
right I saw things that I thought I
could do marketing and branding that
they weren't doing luckily with all that
Blood Sweat and Tears within a year and
a half we tripled the numbers and we
grew it enough to where in 2012 it made
sense for me to flip it you know and
then move on but when from the outside
what people have to understand when
you're an entrepreneur and you have that
in your DNA you can't work for somebody
else you're going to feel smothered but
that's okay most people are going to
look at you like you're crazy but here's
what you have to understand this is so
vitally important you're the one with
the fog lights see you there's it's
going to be so foggy M to see that
destination right to see that end result
but you're the one with the fog lights
everyone else around you they just can't
see through that fog light you can
because this is your destination this is
your idea this is your dream so when you
can hold on to that and keep moving
forward right and understand that action
is magical see massive effective action
becomes magical the people and the
circumstances come into your life to
start to make unfold and like Martin
Luther King said you don't have to see
the whole staircase you just got to see
The Next Step mhm and I was saying that
yesterday with Stacy across she came on
and you know uh a lot of people dig
themselves into holes and sometimes we
we walk into holes that we're not aware
of but you know we have to find a way to
dig it out and you know when you're in a
big hole that you think that you can't
get out of you're not thinking to make
that you you're thinking well [ __ ] I
wish I had you know wish I had longer
legs so I could just hop out but life is
not like that you got to dig stairs you
know you got to dig your way out by just
creating stairs you can take a shovel or
you can take your hands and and it will
take time but you know just one one one
step at a time and I think that that's
brilliant so when you started your first
business did you were you were you born
into money did you have money um like
where did you get the money to do your
first business no actually uh no it
definitely not born into money and not
uh we weren't we weren't extremely poor
but we weren't extremely rich we were uh
probably lower middle class right if you
will um and my dad was very very frugal
so even if he had money he he wasn't
parting with it um and it was all about
hard work lacing up your boots and
getting to work and you know my first
business I had a business partner and we
just we just it was a it was a public
adjusting firm and I did all the sales
and he did the adjusting the back end
and honestly we started it with a few
thousand that we had scraped together
and how we got this going is I work
seven days a week to bring in work for
us and that's how there was no business
loans no no Dad or Mom or Grandma or
grandpa that had money and and gave it
to us or lent it to us everything was
Sweat Equity 100% Sweat Equity and um
listen that and here's what I think
separates a real entrepreneur from a
Wann toe entrepreneur
resourcefulness when you can tap into
resources when it looks like there's
nothing there that's what separates the
the real from The Pretenders right
because it's easy to fold when you say
well why didn't that business work why
didn't have this why didn't have that so
you're saying that you couldn't come up
with the resources when you needed them
that's what separates a real
entrepreneur from somebody that wants to
be an entrepreneur but it's not really
in your DNA and here's one thing I want
to really get you know and I'm and I'm
I'm such a I take this from Gary ve
because he made such a great point
understand who you are first if you're
not that lead
entrepreneur the sooner you get that the
EAS the better it's going to be for you
because like he talks about if you're
number two You're Number Eight you're
number six you're number 10 in Facebook
you're still killing it but that's your
world you might not be you know Zuck
Zuckerberg right but you could be number
four in Facebook and I just think that's
a that's such a great thing and where's
that map to that maps to your to who you
are your own level of awareness in
yourself and I think that's so important
to get out there because as you know
Ryan better than
anybody what's the most common word we
hear today in the last five years is
startup startup startup startup startup
start well yeah that's great you you you
can get some money you could you could
you could bring somebody in that has
money they're going to get a piece of
your business but if you don't how to
execute that money's going to dry up
that's right then now what you just
burnt Bridges you just lost you a major
thing in your in your name right and
you're going to go back and work for
somebody maybe that's where you should
have been to begin with either way right
that's okay but understand who you are
so I think that's a very important Point
here so when it comes to planning a
business and putting all that stuff
together not everyone knows how to be uh
resourceful I mean because I like for me
I I was in sales since I was 12 so like
I I know how to uh to find the resources
I know how to get my way through through
certain adverse sit situations but not
everybody has that ability to do that so
like what would what would be your
response to that like how do do you have
to be born with that ability to
recognize those opportunities to be an
entrepreneur or can that be taught can
that be something that people can learn
to recognize well I think it I think may
maybe a small part of that might be able
to be taught but I think it really comes
down to you when you're the DNA and also
I'm a huge huge huge believer in your
why see I believe that when your why
becomes big enough it's going to pull
you through those fear barriers it's
going to pull you through those
struggles and when your why becomes
bigger than you whatever that is when
your why becomes bigger than you you
become Unstoppable now we're painting a
pretty broad brush here because when I
talk about that Ryan I'm talking about
life not just business right so that
single mom that has three kids
struggling check the check but she's
getting up at 4:30 in the morning to get
things done and she gets home at 7 just
to because her why is big enough because
it's her family right and she's working
that second job or that third job or
working that part-time job from home
right whatever your why is it has to be
big enough and I always tell people look
if you can't identify your why and it's
not big enough you got to stop stop go
back find out why so tell me what is
your your why like why did you why did
you start Dave daily the monster
motivator I mean every day I I want to
say like every day I have to go through
the hustle Zone group and I got to click
check check check check check check all
this all this all these different memes
got your picture on there got a message
but you're really aggressive and you
have to have something that is driving
you beyond belief so you you need to
tell us the skinny give us the real the
of why you do what you do well you know
personal development changed my life and
probably saved my life about 17 years
ago when I got introduced to it through
marriage counseling and uh I've never
stopped learning and and keeping in my
life now there was times in these 17
years that I might have not had it in my
life as much and I noticed such a
difference right so it's all about that
lifestyle change so I all I tell people
is I'm not a mentor I'm not a CO coach
I'm not a business coach I'm a student
that's sharing what was taught to me and
take what works and throw out the rest
that's that's the bottom line uh but
personal development is everything it's
the end all of life okay that I love
that answer but that's a little bit too
vague for me I I honestly you are so
aggressive with your marketing campaigns
that there has to be something even
deeper than that you know well then it
goes back to branding 101 right branding
101 is never let them forget you right
and if you if you
truly believe in what you're doing you
believe in your message you know your
content then you can't get it out enough
everything that you see we're getting
ready to ramp this up in 2017 that's
going to make 2016 look like nobody knew
who I was I am I'm I'm ready to actually
just ramp this thing up to a whole
another level I'll give you a great
example I I get asked to join groups a
lot Facebook groups and and some of
these Facebook groups after about a
month they'll come back to me and I'll
get an instant message and they'll say
oh wait a minute wait um uh uh you got
to slow down on your post because it's
becoming Dave daily monster motivator
group so my response is that's fine I
don't belong here but you might want to
ask yourself and maybe ask your people
why it is that you want somebody to slow
down and go back down to your level
instead of you trying to crank it up to
somebody else's level and it's either
one of two things Ryan or it's a
combination of the two the real is they
don't know their content they don't
believe in their content or they're just
too lazy or it's a combination of the
two and everything that you see
everything that you see right now I do
from my phone live every post my
marketing girl I pick the quotes she
puts the images together puts them in my
dve drop box and everything that you see
when I post at 12:00 today that's coming
from my phone it's not a hoot site it's
not buffer it's coming from my phone now
my emails are set up by her but what you
see on inst what you see on person uh on
uh social media that's coming that's
coming from the horse's mouth my man oh
yeah I add it comes right to me at that
moment there's nothing preset that's why
monster motivator TV be is becoming my
oxygen right people say well are you g
to send me questions are you no just
send me your bio and we are going to go
real wrong live and I'm going to ask you
questions as they come to me a lot like
you're doing and you can't you can't
beat that realness you can't beat that
energy and I mean like that's the thing
I was saying that yesterday is that you
know um I've lost a lot of friends uh or
like you know they I think they've
ignored me or whatever but I'm like this
the cheapest cheapest way the cheapest
way to get rid of a uh bad friend or
waste waste you know to get rid of waste
is to be consistent right you know you
know what scares people the most is the
future people are scared of
robots because they're they're scared of
consistency they're they're scared that
they would be able to manipulate
themselves through a job you know I've
hired when I was a sales manager I've
hired so many people that had degrees I
didn't I left High School didn't
graduate don't have a diploma and yet
I'm hiring engineers and all kinds of of
people that are apparently supposed to
be super smart but can't do basic work
because you know not I don't know what
what their motivation was but it wasn't
strong enough for them to be consistent
so you know I'm all for that it's either
you rev your game up or you let people
dominate you and that's what I see that
you're dominating uh the situation so
you know a lot of people say and I'm
going to ask you this a lot of people
say well
Dave I'm not like you you I can't do
what you do and you're motivating them
you're getting them all revved up but
what do you tell them when you know when
they say well I just it's just not me I
don't think I can do that kind of stuff
well you know and and so my answer to to
them would be then you're moving in you
already made the right step see you're
starting to identify who you are and I
always say understand who you are so you
can enhance your weaknesses so you can
run with your strengths whatever that is
I found out when I got into the real
world thank God right for this ran I
thank God every day for this that in the
real world EQ Trump's IQ all day long
because my IQ is way behind my EQ but it
works out much better in the real world
man and thank God it sometimes better be
lucky than good my man and uh it just
worked out that way so so my answer
would be you you're starting to
understand who you are great if you're
that backend person right that keeps
everything in in line in the business
then that's who you are then run with
that promote yourself in that way guess
what I I'm the guy in the front I need
those people in the back I need those
people that are going to keep everything
in order so I can double down triple
down quadruple down on my strengths and
that's being in the front so now that
make sense yeah that makes a lot of
sense and I think um um self-awareness
it don't matter what you do but
self-awareness just do the do the best
that you can um I had an early podcast
today and I said to everyone like hey
folks don't plan to to to fail plan to
win you know that reason why your ideas
are not working why your life is not
working because you already committed to
yourself when you're writing your plan
ah they may not like this ah this is too
much they Pro this is probably too high
so already you had a good idea but then
you had to dial it back because you were
afraid that you wouldn't be able to
succeed so I think that you know truly
understanding um who you are and what's
going to make you happy Live Your
Passion but do the best job at it
because who wants to do their passion
half ass I don't know anyone that wants
to do that um I was I'm going to kind of
flip the change the the the conversation
here and I want to get to know you I
want to I want to know what like all cuz
I mean Dave daily the monster motivator
is
24/7 so on the few hours that you do get
to your yourself what do you do uh well
I'm up at my alarm goes off at 4:30
every morning 7 days a week I'm at the
gym um and that's my hour of that's my
zen that's and that's seven days a week
uh unless I'm traveling and then if I
have to do it later in the day but
that's my zen that's that's that's
that's my centering and then from there
my day unfolds and one of the things I
love um I'm a big MMA guy I love um MMA
and I love the UFC so my downtime would
be like that Saturday night pay-per-view
uh MMA um uh fight either going there or
or watching it uh with with friends uh
but but honestly I'm a worker man I'm my
assistant called me it was a Sunday two
weeks ago like 3 o'clock in the
afternoon and she said I just want to
make sure I'm not bothering I said Cindy
I have no boundaries look to me Sunday
is just like a Tuesday and that's and
understanding see getting back to what
you said about your own level of
awareness that might not work for
everybody right Sunday might be your day
for your family you got to figure that
out right and and mold around that for
me if I got stuff to do I'm getting [ __ ]
done on Sunday right it's quiet I'm G to
knock it out and then move forward and I
also have another business that I run I
have a fire restoration business out
here so you know a lot of balls in the
air but that's what that's my oxygen
that's what keeps me interested and I
realized when I got out of high school
when I could look back and clear my head
and start to see success I realized that
they just didn't they didn't keep my
attention I was bored out of my mind you
don't know why I was bored because I
didn't see any purpose I didn't see any
end result when you're running when
you're starting a business there's a
purpose there's a direction there's a
road map and then there's a destination
right for school it's like you're just
going through the motions understand the
basics right the reading uh math the
basic skills that has to be implemented
but everything after that really should
be somehow customized to that person man
because because I was bored out of my
mind and that's most entrepreneurs they
and we hate to be told what to do that's
right it's an our DNA and I was going to
just mention that because a lot of uh
people think that we're
self-absorbed um especially if we're in
the public eye and we're speaking and
and whatnot and yes I am
self-absorbed because you know I believe
believe that that's just my level of
confidence however there's always a
however there are people in our life
that keep us
balanced who's the people who who are
the people in your life that's keeping
you balanced that keep you put you in
check man I'll be honest with you man I
don't I don't have that I don't I I um I
have some a handful of really good
friends um I have a lot of acquaintances
um and I just and I have you know a very
small uh family uh but yeah I I just um
I'm I just do me man and that's that's
really honestly I just do me now now
doesn't mean I'm not making mistakes
doesn't mean I'm not falling down but I
promise you I do get up and brush myself
off and move forward so um and it kind
of goes back to Ryan about when you ask
me you know where did you start to see
that uniqueness in yourself and even as
a little kid I would just internalize
things I'm a thinker I'm constantly you
know what I realized Ryan when I got
older is that I have one of the things
besides the gym I I need and live and
breathe on motion therapy whether that's
walking walking my dog or in my truck
just driving man my mind I get the best
ideas I get the clearest I need to be
moving the hardest thing for me is being
in this office for any length of time
right so I got to surround myself with
the people that love this and hate to be
out out there right because I need I
need Like Oxygen uh motion therapy man
need it I I remember that um you know
what what has made me do what I do like
I've I've been in business for three
years on my own and um I was went
through a breakup with my with my son's
mother and that was really devastating
to me but the one thing that I didn't do
is I didn't let it get me down that
actually gave me a lot of fuel that you
wouldn't believe it was just this
determination that you know what one of
these days I'm going to be a
[ __ ] billionaire and excuse my
language I have a swear jar folks and I
am getting that ready for you guys so
every time I swear it goes into the
swear jar and we're going to give away
for for uh for charity but I you know
like that's what drives me every day not
because I'm you know that I miss her I
mean I'm happy that she's moved on and
and I've moved on but it was I that's
when I was able to connect in that Chi
that moment where I realized that and
you if you know martial arts and what
not like there's a lot of inner I was in
martial arts when I was young and that
Chi we interpret that Chi to be
sometimes it's negative especially when
something negative happens to you but
it's just energy and when you can
channel that
energy and you know when to release it
and when to hold it back you have full
control over the things that happen in
your life so you can internally motivate
yourself on a constant basis because
that energy whether you're using it or
not it's always there so how do you
hardness your
tea you know it's it's all about G
building your level of awareness and
that's really what you did over the last
three years and that's what personal
development helped me with and I'm going
to share this with you the proudest
thing I've ever done in my life business
or or personal Bar None not not even a
second place me and my wife were
together my ex-wife were together 17
years married and together 17 years we
went through a divorce but because the
personal development was so started to
be so ingrained in my life that we split
the business split the uh properties
right down the middle no attorneys and
we still talk to this day and I'm still
really close with her family because
personal development helped me grow as a
person as an individual it help my my
level of awareness in myself grow and I
wouldn't even come close to being able
to do that before personal development
so there's another part of my passion
and my why on why I want to share this
information with people it literally um
change my life he said share I heard
share that's a secret word blink blink
blink share share share so make sure you
guys are sharing this podcast this is
the realest this is the
realest like you know hustle Zone that
we've ever done because you know he's
given us all he's given us the raw
information that we need to to just
build our life to get to the next level
so uh
Dave what are your fears like like
everyone has it like I mean you're a big
guy I mean I'm the fear barrier guy
right what am I afraid of what are you
afraid of I am terrified
absolutely utterly terrified not even a
second place of
regret I am not getting to the end
whether that's today or whe that's 50
years from now I am not getting to the
end looking back saying should have
would have could have it's not even an
option we are if I have to jump off the
cliff build a plane on the way down
that's what I got to do and I've done it
and I've crashed and I've flown so
that's that's what life is about you
know it's about what I always say Ryan
is life is a is a dance it's always
moving in and out of form right we know
that but also it's perspective it's
perception so when you can look at a
risk and you can look at this uh next
Journey instead of in a fearful State
more in an adventurous state right you
get this shot you get this one chance at
life you get one ride why would you ever
not want to make it the biggest baddest
ride ever it doesn't make sense when you
get to that end and you look back if you
look back and regret you can't get that
time back doesn't matter how rich you
are doesn't matter how smart you are it
doesn't matter how good-look you are
when you get to the end you can't get it
back it's gone today today when it's
over it's gone tomorrow I know you're in
Canada tomorrow is Thanksgiving here
right when it's over it's in the books
baby it's done it's history you can't
buy uh Thanksgiving 2016 back
once it's
over that's what I want to get to people
you that message this is your one ride
this is it you got to you got to take
the reins never give up the driver's
seat in your ride and I I mean I'm gonna
get political
here but this the hustle all we don't
care keep
real I I can tell you that um I'm going
to disclose to everybody that was not I
was a fan of trump before he ran for for
presidency and then I I was not a fan um
you know me being a visible minority and
and all those things however I just
wasn't fan of how you ran the
campaign I I'm a Libertarian slash you
know I lean more right than I do lean
left but the I wasn't a fan of the
rhetoric Etc on both sides of the
parties and I'm not even American but I
we were all watching here Trump
Illustrated something that was pretty
profound and and a lot of people don't
even want to hear it when I bring it up
they like uh I don't want to hear it but
when when he was dealing with the the
scandal with him talking about women in
in a derogatory way um he had an opp he
had an opportunity I think that was the
worst part of the campaign um and people
were giving him that opportunity to
leave to
quit and Trump said and he and I've
known this because I followed Trump for
many years um Trump one of the things
that he does not do is
quit and what you've what you've
demonstrated today that you know no
matter what you keep on going and you
never give up you know because I don't
have to agree with what you're saying
but you know the people that win are the
ones that never quit
and what can you like how could like
with this this political campaign what
were the things that you observed
that people can apply to their lives cuz
that's what I applied with I like I'm
trying to find the positive out of all
what had happened I mean it's politics
but what did you observe from that
situation um and how can we apply that
to our personal lives well you know
first and foremost was um people are
starving for real and whether you like
them or not um it didn't matter to him
he's going to keep it real he's going to
tell you exactly how he feels and here's
the other thing there's a lot of stuff
being said by him um on the platform in
Twitter whatever here's what I respect
about first of all business-wise people
are like how is he doing this right
because politics are so dirty they're so
rough they're so ruthless are you
kidding me 40 years dominating the
Manhattan New York City skyline are you
kid you're that's he's a great white in
a sea of sharks you can't become that
successful in Manhattan commercial real
estate without being a shark and not
only a shark a great white so this stuff
man this you're you're playing into his
world this is his world right that's
like talking about Conor McGregor and
Mayweather you get in that ring without
an octagon with just gloves on and you
can't kick and you think you're going to
step up the Mayweather you're in a
different world but you flip that around
you're allowed to kick you're in an
octagon and you can take this to the
ground he's going to get dominated so
Trump was in his world and they didn't
even realize it but what I think
happened is he kept it real and there
was things that he said that maybe you
don't agree with maybe I don't agree
with maybe somebody else don't agree
with but I promise you this if you went
behind a black curtain and you listen to
people talk when the camera's not on
it's a lot of lot of the same stuff is
being said he just happened to say it
and kept it real another another person
that you can mod after that created a un
a billion doll brand is Howard Stern
Howard Stern kept it real and he said
and and guess what he said this is who I
am like it or not and he people would
call in and be just screaming at him he
would say stop following me and what I
learned is the haters are your biggest
fans that's that's why you're on their
radar so much but I learned getting back
to Trump man I I just learned that
keeping it real um is the only option
it's the only way to go cuz guess what
everything he said he meant right or
wrong agree with him or not so if when
that campaign was over he could look
himself in a mirror and that's all that
matters that's all that matters I always
say keep it real here's the thing
Ryan I do I do uh uh corporate speaking
and you see me my brand when I walk into
a corporate setting I just did one in La
Hoya when I walk into that corporate
setting they're trying to figure out
where who what is this guy right did he
come from Mars where did he's not our he
can't be our motivational speaker and as
this talk goes on you start to see the
faces change you start to see the body
language change and then after it's just
they look at me completely different but
here's the deal we're human so we are
going to make judgment based on what we
see that's we're human right
your
job is to keep it real so you keep them
accurate that's right that's right drop
the
mic right I mean there's two things that
I always say it's like there's two
relationships that you need to have a
relationship with yourself you need to
know yourself you need to love yourself
but you also need a relationship with
your pillow because at the end of the
day you got to sleep at night you know
what I mean and and there's a lot of
people not keeping it real and then
they're up at night because they're
trying to figure out how to how how to
get out of those situations and you know
and that's what you're pretty much
demonstrating is that you're saying hey
keep it real to yourself to keep
yourself happy because if we are angry
if we at if we're in discontent with
ourselves how can we focus on the future
how can we focus on anything we can only
focus on one thought in the time and if
it's a negative thought we're not we're
not going to go anywhere until that's
resolved and the only way it's resolved
is when you keep it real and you like
sometimes you're going to piss people
off I'm not saying that this this
lifestyle that we live is sweet
but understand just take the
consequences why do we have to struggle
with the consequences just take it you
know what I mean I think Trump was an
example of a guy that just you know he
took it you know he he I don't he didn't
own up to half of the stuff but still he
took what it was and then he served it
back and I think a lot of people don't
can't stomach just standing up for
themselves and for their actions and
some people just don't take
accountability for their actions they
don't change there was a person that
said hey don't apologize just act just
do you know don't go ahead 100% and
here's the thing let's really dig dig
even deeper than that why is that why
does that happen where do lies manifest
you know where lies manifest in fear see
if someone's not being real that means
they're afraid to show who they really
are if somebody's lying about something
they're afraid to show the truth see the
truth is
courageous a lie is based in fear and
fear can never win long term you know
why because the greatest equalizer on
our planet on our universe is time time
always tells the
truth W okay I'm gonna stop there we
just this is too much we have to stop it
on that note
uh Dave Dave wow I hope you enjoyed the
hustle Zone I don't know if you knew
what you were expecting last night we
cut you off real quick cuz I only have
50 minutes on the Shane train show and
he's play probably wondering like who's
this C Ryan you know what I mean like
this guy's out to lunch then he wants me
to comment he asked okay folks he asked
me if this is going to be a five minute
show or he was going to ask me how long
is the show and I said five minutes I
said I thought it was a typo like what
cuz it is I tell people five minutes
like I about five minutes of your time
and it usually comes out better than
that so how did you like the experience
with the hustle loved it man loved it
cuz you know why you just rolled with it
we kept it real rolling live and like I
said before we went on nothing's off the
table let's just get them behind that
black curtain and that's what I want to
share with people with my show as well
and I'm sure you run into this when you
want to get behind that black curtain
people run you know why because they're
running from their story instead of
understanding that your story is not
about you your story is about the other
people that you can help you were bad
enough to make it through that story now
it's your obligation to share that story
that's right woo okay more he's dropping
more he's giving this is like he gave
value and now he's just giving Extra
Value right so like this is this is this
is amazing so we're going to go uh and
look at some of these comments here
because to be honest with you we
wouldn't have a hustle Zone people
wouldn't be tuning in hadn't it not been
for um yeah and I got I got a bunch too
so I'll I'll read something from my list
you read something from your list okay
so we got I just want to say hi to
Patrick ban built uh Terren uh lej uh
Breezy uh
Tracy uh I some of these names I can't
pronounce bum Nissa Chad Johnny thank
you guys all for liking um and then we
had four shares
here I want to thank myself for Shar
Dave keep sh going Tracy Terren thank
you guys so much uh just write reading
some of the list here uh Terren is
powerful my brothers well thank you
Terrence yep you can J you can't judge a
book of course you can um what did uh
Frank said he's going to be great for
this nation because he's a model for a
real essence of masterminding that that
must be in regards to Trump um and uh
who else there's just a lot of comments
here um okay EQ so here's a book on EQ
versus IQ recommend it Champs it's uh it
helped me I'm listening to emotional
intelligence 2.0 by Travis Bradberry So
yeah thank you very much Terence for
sharing so yeah folks thank you guys for
contributing on on on if you guys have
any questions for for Dave uh the master
motivator or not the master the monster
motivator he's also the master uh let us
know and then yeah Dave if you want to
address some of comments on your end
Jasmine thank you so much Jasmine Bryan
She says get it done Dave Chris Ripka
man we're going to do some great things
together coming up in 2017 I'm so pumped
that we connected man John pal um he
says uh I choose not to be a common man
it's my right to be uncommon if I can um
and you're absolutely right man you
gotta in order to stand out you got to
learn how to step out and if you're not
willing to step out you can't stand out
and you can't bring your real game uh
Gloria M madrano Gloria thank you so
much I thank you so much for the support
and she says uh truth is uh courageous
heck yeah you know lies come fear um
also Marin that's my monster moderator
she's the one that uh we have her on
speaker phone she gives us all the
comments when we're on live with monster
motivator TV Wade Bloodgood awesome
awesome man um and uh and Gloria thank
you again um for jumping on and comments
and we got uh Frankie Lane Janette
Janette that's my girl she's making it
happen out here in San Diego Carl uh G
son I love his uh check this guy out in
the mornings he's got the best um
insights he posts every morning awesome
awesome stuff um keeping it real Bruna
Martins Bruna that's my girl from
Connecticut always uh always making it
happen uh thank you for the support Pat
Hilton thanks for jumping on uh so there
you go man we got uh got a lot of people
loving this if you guys get value share
this get this out there um because this
is stuff that people to understand how
to implement their life on a consistent
basis man most definitely and uh would
you come back to the hustle
Zone 100% man 100% and we're going to
put this out here right when we go
Nationwide worldwide with the monster
motivator Mania tour coming to a town
near you we are going to have you on
when we get up to Canada baby we're
gonna have you
on and live well I would love to be I
would love to take part my friends so
thank you guys so much uh for
participating in the show today uh and
Dave I'm going to send you a link to the
show that so you can share it on your
page and um Dave how how about how about
we how about we take this out monster
motivator style yes let's do it here how
we do it you ready we're gonna do the
monster motivator Roar now I believe
that you can only be in one state of
mind at a time so if you're in victim
State you can't be in gratitude state if
you're in gratitude State there's no
room for victim state but if you could
be in Unstoppable State the majority of
your day how good would that be Ryan be
great be awesome would that be badass
that'd be badass that would that would
be badass and life always makes the
rules in life says Ryan do you want to
Pearl like a kitten or roar like a lion
roar my man so we're GNA take it out
monster motivator style this is the
monster motivator Roar are you familiar
yes I seen it last night okay so here we
go baby all three one two three
a I feel stupid but yeah man it's
awesome that's it brother that was
awesome you guys probably see some of
the cavities in my mouth and everything
good Lord okay so Lov it brother so
thank you so much appreciate it how can
we find you Dave da mm Dave da d e y mm
like monster motivator on all my social
media and uh you can check us out uh
knockout fear in the first round on
Amazon and I'll also post that link uh
when we reshare this and again man I
appreciate your time brother yeah no
problem well thank you so much just one